Guide to the Miscellaneous Manuscripts Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- E - G, Series III
  - Esmein, Adhemar, 1876-1909, undated (Box 22, Folder 421)
  - Eustis, William, 1810-1812 (Box 22, Folder 422)
  - Evans, Charles, 1952-1963 (Box 22, Folder 423)
  - Evans, David and Contenta, 1831 (Box 22, Folder 424)
  - Evans, John family, 1868-1902 (Box 22, Folder 425)
  - Evans, Montgomery, 1949 (Box 22, Folder 426)
  - Everard, Nathaniel, 1934 (Box 22, Folder 427)
  - Fabyan, Samuel, undated (Box 22, Folder 428)
  - Fagan, Leo J., 1933 (Box 22, Folder 429)
  - Fairbanks, Douglas Elton Jr., undated (Box 22, Folder 430)
  - Fairchild, Julia Ann, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 431)
  - Farmers Mutual Fire Insurance Co., N.H., 1857 (Box 22, Folder 432)
  - Farnam, William D., 1968 (Box 23, Folder 433)
  - Farnam, William D., 1968 (Box 23, Folder 434)
  - Farnsley, Alexander, 1856-1860 (Box 23, Folder 435)
  - Farrington, John, 1753 (Box 23, Folder 436)
  - Fay, James Herbert, 1938 (Box 23, Folder 437)
  - Fay, Theodore Sedgewick, 1874 (Box 23, Folder 438)
  - Fenollosa, Ernest Francisco, 1908 (Box 23, Folder 439)
  - Fergusson, Thomas T., 1876 (Box 23, Folder 440)
  - Fernando V, el Católico, King of Spain, 1495 (Box 23, Folder 441)
  - Ferry, Oris Sanford, 1875 (Box 23, Folder 442)
  - Ferry Family, 1833-1864 (Box 23, Folder 443)
  - Fiedler, Carl, 1875 (Box 23, Folder 444)
  - Figg, F. G., 1907 (Box 23, Folder 445)
  - Filchner, William, 1903 (Box 23, Folder 446)
  - Finley, John Huston, 1922 (Box 23, Folder 447)
  - Fish, Hamilton, 1875, 1889 (Box 23, Folder 448)
  - Fisher, Robert A., 1860 (Box 23, Folder 449)
  - Fitch, James, 1676 (Box 23, Folder 450)
  - Fitch, Martin, undated (Box 23, Folder 451)
  - Fitch, Thomas, 1696 (Box 23, Folder 452)
  - Fitzgerald, O. E., 1877 (Box 23, Folder 453)
  - Fleischner, Charles Maurice, 1936-1949 (Box 23, Folder 454)
    General
    Transferred to the Charles Maurice Fleischner Papers, Ms. Gr. 1466.
  - Fleming, William, 1800 (Box 23, Folder 455)
  - Flügel, Johann Gottfried, 1866 (Box 23, Folder 456)
  - Flynt, Eudocia Carter Converse, 1847-1848 (Box 23, Folder 457)
  - Folger, Lamb and Co., 1831 (Box 23, Folder 458)
  - Foot, Solomon, 1857 (Box 23, Folder 459)
  - Footner, Hulbert, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 460)
  - Force, Peter, 1845 (Box 23, Folder 461)
  - Ford, Gerald R., 1976 (Box 23, Folder 462)
  - Ford, Samuel C., 1833 (Box 23, Folder 463)
  - Foster, John Watson, 1895 (Box 23, Folder 464)
  - Foster, Warren, 1884 (Box 24, Folder 465)
  - Foucher, Alfred Charles Auguste, 1895 (Box 24, Folder 466)
  - Fox, Charles James, undated (Box 24, Folder 467)
  - France, 1465, 1744, 1787 (Box 24, Folder 468-470)
  - Frank, Tenney, 1904-1905 (Box 24, Folder 471)
  - Franklin, Ruford, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 472)
  - Frazer, Abraham Carpenter, 1827 (Box 24, Folder 473)
  - Frazer, William C., 1813 (Box 24, Folder 474)
  - Frederick II, King of Prussia, undated (Box 24, Folder 475)
  - Freeman, Capt., 1789 (Box 24, Folder 476)
  - Frelinghuysen, Theodore, 1838 (Box 24, Folder 477)
  - Freemasons Miscellanea, 1786-1926, undated (Box 24, Folder 478)
  - Fremont, John Charles, undated (Box 24, Folder 479)
  - Frémont, Julia, undated (Box 24, Folder 480)
  - Freneau, Peter, 1805 (Box 24, Folder 481)
  - Friedrich Wilhelm, Elector of Brandenburg, 1670 (Box 24, Folder 482)
  - Friend, John, undated (Box 24, Folder 483)
  - Friends, Society of, 1842 (Box 24, Folder 484)
  - Fry, Thomas, 1863 (Box 24, Folder 485)
  - Fudger, Henry H., 1919 (Box 24, Folder 486)
  - Fuller, Ephraim, 1790 (Box 24, Folder 487)
  - Fullerton, William Morton, 1908 (Box 24, Folder 488)
  - Furniss, Edgar Stephenson, 1933, 1949 (Box 24, Folder 489)
  - Furniss, Todd, 1932-1933 (Box 24, Folder 490)
  - Gage, Matilda Ann (Baker), 1836-1903 (Box 24, Folder 491)
  - Gallo, Giovanni Battista, undated (Box 25, Folder 492)
  - Gardiner, Charles, 1849-1854 (Box 25, Folder 493)
  - Garfield, James Abram, 1872 (Box 25, Folder 494)
  - Garrett, Oliver, 1836 (Box 25, Folder 495)
  - Garrison, William Lloyd, 1829-1878 (Box 25, Folder 496)
  - Garrison, William Lloyd Jr., 1895 (Box 25, Folder 497)
  - Gatfield, Benjamin, 1790 (Box 25, Folder 498)
  - Gelston, Maltby, 1819 (Box 25, Folder 499)
  - George, John H., 1852 (Box 25, Folder 500)
  - Georgia, 1833-1842 (Box 25, Folder 501)
  - German MSS, 1413, 1868, 1915-1918, 1936 (Box 25, Folder 502)
  - Gibson, Hugh Simons, 1904, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 503-504)
  - Gibson, William, 1919 (Box 25, Folder 505)
  - Gilbert, Harold Arthur, 1940-1944 (Box 25, Folder 506)
  - Gilmore, James Roberts, 1888 (Box 25, Folder 507)
  - Gimbel, Richard, 1956, 1962, undated (Box 25, Folder 508)
  - Glaser, Lewis, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 509)
  - Gleason, Frederick, 1852 (Box 25, Folder 510)
  - Glenn, John C. Collection, 1799, 1836-1857, undated (Box 25, Folder 511)
  - Glenn, John F., 1935-1936 (Box 25, Folder 512)
  - Gloden, Albert, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 513)
  - Gobrecht, Charles Joseph, 1846 (Box 25, Folder 514)
  - Godwin, Parke, 1874 (Box 25, Folder 515)
  - Gokhale, Dattatraya Vasudeo, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 516)
  - Goodale, C. Louise, 1894 (Box 25, Folder 517)
  - Goodwin Family, 1795-1846 (Box 25, Folder 518)
  - Gorges, Ferdinando, 1664 (Box 25, Folder 519)
  - Gotlieb, Howard Bernard, 1945-1961 (Box 25, Folder 520)
  - Gottlieb, Adolph, undated (Box 25, Folder 521)
  - Gould, John, 1835-1843 (Box 25, Folder 522)
  - Graham, George, undated (Box 25, Folder 523)
  - Granger, Gideon, 1801 (Box 25, Folder 524)
  - Granniss, Ruth Shepard, undated (Box 25, Folder 525)
  - Grant, Anne (Macvicar), undated (Box 26, Folder 526)
  - Graves, Robert, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 527)
  - Greeley, Horace, 1846, 1863, 1872 (Box 26, Folder 528)
  - Greely, Adolphus Washington, 1884 (Box 26, Folder 529)
  - Gregg, John Robert, undated (Box 26, Folder 530)
  - Greifswald Universität, 1730 (Box 26, Folder 531)
  - Griffin, Edward Dorr, 1832 (Box 26, Folder 532)
  - Griswold, George W., 1828 (Box 26, Folder 533)
  - Griswold, Harvey D., 1925-1926, undated (Box 26, Folder 534)
  - Griswold, Sarah, 1840 (Box 26, Folder 535)
  - Grout, Franklin, 1904 (Box 26, Folder 536)
  - Guerchy, Comte De, 1764 (Box 26, Folder 537)
  - Guernsey Family Collection, 1856-1859, undated (Box 26, Folder 538)
  - Guinet, Charles, 1917-1918 (Box 26, Folder 539)
  - Guyot, Arnold Henry, 1872 (Box 26, Folder 540)
- H - J, Series IV
  - Haasis, Julius, 1842 (Box 27, Folder 541)
  - Hackney, Louise Wallace, 1933-1934, undated (Box 27, Folder 542-543)
  - Hadley, Arthur Twining, 1887-1927 (Box 27, Folder 544)
  - Haile Sellassie I, Emperor of Ethiopia, 1940 (Box 27, Folder 545)
  - Hale, David, 1802 (Box 27, Folder 546)
  - Hale, Samuel, 1784 (Box 27, Folder 547)
  - Hall, A. M., undated (Box 27, Folder 548)
  - Hall, Loly (Turner), undated (Box 27, Folder 549)
  - Hall, Nathan F., 1852-1855 (Box 27, Folder 550)
  - Hamilton, James 3rd Marquis, 1664 (Box 27, Folder 551)
  - Hamlin, Hannibal, 1876, 1879 (Box 27, Folder 552)
  - Hammond, Charles, 1838 (Box 27, Folder 553)
  - Hammond, Fanny (Reed), 1937-1938 (Box 27, Folder 554)
  - Hammond, Josephus, 1754 (Box 27, Folder 555)
  - Hancock, Winfield Scott, 1879 (Box 27, Folder 556)
  - Haring, John, 1802 (Box 27, Folder 557)
  - Harris, Robert Family, 1748-1776 (Box 27, Folder 558)
  - Harrison, Benjamin, 1857-1896 (Box 27, Folder 559)
  - Harrison, Gabriel, 1884 (Box 27, Folder 560)
  - Harrison, Mary (Lord), 1932 (Box 27, Folder 561)
  - Hart, Burdett, undated (Box 27, Folder 562)
  - Harte, Bret, 1872 (Box 27, Folder 563)
  - Harte, Charles Rufus, 1910-1940, 1944, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 564-565)
  - Hartley, Edward, 1868-1869 (Box 28, Folder 566)
  - Harvard University, 1830 (Box 28, Folder 567)
  - Harwood, Edwin, 1887, undated (Box 28, Folder 568)
  - Hastings, John, 1851 (Box 28, Folder 569)
  - Hatch, Nathaniel, 1749 (Box 28, Folder 570)
  - Haupt, Paul, 1884 (Box 28, Folder 571)
  - Hawkins, Nana Pratt, 1920 (Box 28, Folder 572)
  - Hawley, Gideon, 1738 (Box 28, Folder 573)
  - Hawley, James, 1834-1838 (Box 28, Folder 574)
  - Hawley, John Baldwin, 1869-1874 (Box 28, Folder 575)
  - Hawley, Joseph Roswell, 1856-1903, undated (Box 28, Folder 576)
  - Haynes, Milton A., 1844 (Box 28, Folder 577)
  - Hazard, Thomas, 1811-1816 (Box 28, Folder 578)
  - Henke, Karl, 1931 (Box 28, Folder 579)
  - Henriques, Philip family, 1796-1845, undated (Box 29, Folder 580-581)
  - Henriques, Robert David Quixano, 1945 (Box 29, Folder 582)
  - Hersey, Abba Fletcher, 1840 (Box 29, Folder 583)
  - Heyward, Thomas Jr., 1785 (Box 29, Folder 584)
  - Hicks, Thomas, 1864 (Box 29, Folder 585)
  - Higgins, Frank Wayland, 1903-1905 (Box 29, Folder 586)
  - Higginson, Thomas Wentworth, 1886 (Box 29, Folder 587)
  - Hildreth, Azro Benjamin Franklin, 1906 (Box 29, Folder 588)
  - Hill, David Bennett, 1904-1905 (Box 29, Folder 589)
  - Hill, Edwin Allston, 1866-1926, undated (Box 29, Folder 590-591)
  - Hill, Phebe W., 1815 (Box 29, Folder 592)
  - Hill, Thomas, 1887 (Box 29, Folder 593)
  - Hillard, George Stillman, 1873 (Box 29, Folder 594)
  - Hilton, Winthrop, 1707 (Box 29, Folder 595)
  - Hinton, Walker, undated (Box 29, Folder 596)
  - Hobbs, Hiram H., 1834, 1857 (Box 29, Folder 597)
  - Hoffman, Josiah Ogden, undated (Box 29, Folder 598)
  - Hoffman, S. W., 1838 (Box 29, Folder 599)
  - Hogeboom, John C., 1817 (Box 29, Folder 600)
  - Holland Family, 1813-1841, undated (Box 29, Folder 601)
  - Holley, Alexander Hamilton, 1861 (Box 29, Folder 602)
  - Hollingshead, John, 1897 (Box 29, Folder 603)
  - Holliston, Mass. Assessors, 1771 (Box 29, Folder 604)
  - Holmes, Oliver Wendell (father and son), 1882-1928 (Box 29, Folder 605)
  - Holt, Hamilton, 1899-1913 (Box 29, Folder 606)
  - Holyoke, Massachusetts, 1852 (Box 29, Folder 607)
  - Hong, Michael Song Chae, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 608)
  - Hooley, Arthur, undated (Box 29, Folder 609)
  - Hooper, Joseph, 1895-1907 (Box 29, Folder 610)
  - Hoover, Herbert Clark, 1932-1962 (Box 29, Folder 611)
  - Hopkins, Samuel Miles, 1879, 1890 (Box 29, Folder 612)
  - Hopkinton Musical Society, N.H., 1828-1837 (Box 30, Folder 613)
  - Hoppin, William Warner, 1861 (Box 30, Folder 614)
  - Horton, Samuel Dana, 1882, 1885 (Box 30, Folder 615)
  - Hosmer, H[arriet] G[oodhue], undated (Box 30, Folder 616)
  - Hotchkiss, Julius, 1848, 1869 (Box 30, Folder 617)
  - Hotchkiss, Lucy, 1837 (Box 30, Folder 618)
  - Hovey Family Collection, 1912-1914 (Box 30, Folder 619)
  - Howard, Alice M., 1912 (Box 30, Folder 620)
  - Howard, John T., 1881, 1886 (Box 30, Folder 621)
  - Howe, Richard, Earl, 1785 (Box 30, Folder 622)
  - Howe, Walter, 1890 (Box 30, Folder 623)
  - Howe and Spalding, 1822 (Box 30, Folder 624)
  - Hubbard, Joseph Stillman, 1842, 1850 (Box 30, Folder 625)
  - Hubbard, Joseph W., 1850 (Box 30, Folder 626)
  - Hubbard, Richard, 1832 (Box 30, Folder 627)
  - Hubbard, Richard Dudley, 1877-1878 (Box 30, Folder 628)
  - Huggins, Samuel, 1787 (Box 30, Folder 629)
  - Hughes, Charles Evans, 1921-1923 (Box 30, Folder 630)
  - Huidekoper, Frederic, 1848-1868 (Box 30, Folder 631)
  - Hull, Isaac, undated (Box 30, Folder 632)
  - Humboldt, Alexandre, Baron von, 1855, 1858 (Box 30, Folder 633)
  - Humphrey, Henry M., undated (Box 30, Folder 634)
  - Humphrey, Marie E. (Ives), 1870-1876, undated (Box 30, Folder 635)
  - Humphreys, David, 1776-1784, undated (Box 30, Folder 636)
  - Humphreys, May, 1921-1926 (Box 30, Folder 637)
  - Huneker, James Gibbons, 1901-1916 (Box 30, Folder 638)
  - [Hunter, ?], 1923 (Box 30, Folder 639)
  - Hunter, Joseph Collection, 1735/1736-1869, undated (Box 30, Folder 640)
  - Huntington, Charles Lathrop, 1862 (Box 31, Folder 641)
  - Huntington, Isaac, 1743/1744-1763 (Box 31, Folder 642)
  - Huntington, Jabez W., undated (Box 31, Folder 643)
  - Huston, G. M., 1869 (Box 31, Folder 644)
  - Hutchinson, Ruth and Lucinda, 1817, 1849 (Box 31, Folder 645)
  - Icelandic Mss., undated (Box 31, Folder 646)
  - Independence (Ship), 1837-1839, undated (Box 31, Folder 647)
  - Ingalls, Joshua King, 1889, undated (Box 31, Folder 648)
  - Ingelow, Jean, undated (Box 31, Folder 649)
  - Ingersoll, Charles Jared, 1842 (Box 31, Folder 650)
  - Ingersoll, Colin Macrae, 1839-1857, undated (Box 31, Folder 651)
  - Ingersoll, Joseph Reed, 1857 (Box 31, Folder 652)
  - Ingersoll, Ralph Isaacs, 1830-1855 (Box 31, Folder 653)
  - Ingham, Samuel, 1820-1858 (Box 31, Folder 654)
  - Ingraham, Edward, 1940, 1945 (Box 31, Folder 655)
  - International Military Tribunal, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 656)
  - Irving, John Duer, 1914-1915 (Box 31, Folder 657)
  - Isabel, La Catòlica, Queen of Spain, 1492 (Box 31, Folder 658)
  - Jackson, Andrew, 1830-1845, undated (Box 31, Folder 659)
  - Jackson, Ebenezer Jr., 1838 (Box 31, Folder 660)
  - Jackson, Eleanor (Junkin), 1902, undated (Box 31, Folder 661)
  - Jackson, Frances G., 1909-1914 (Box 31, Folder 662)
  - Jackson, Jonathan, 1784-1810 (Box 31, Folder 663)
  - Jacocks, Elizabeth, 1814 (Box 32, Folder 664)
  - Jäger, Georg Friedrich von, [1838?]-1841 (Box 32, Folder 665)
  - James, Henry, undated (Box 32, Folder 666)
  - Jameson, C. D., 1861 (Box 32, Folder 667)
  - Janvier, Thomas Allibone, undated (Box 32, Folder 668)
  - Jaszi, Mrs. Oscar, 1959 (Box 32, Folder 669)
  - Jefferson College, Washington, Mississippi, 1842 (Box 32, Folder 670)
  - Jeffries Family Papers, 1707-1778 (Box 32, Folder 671)
  - Jennings, David. "An Introduction to the Knowledge of Medals", undated (Box 32, Folder 672)
  - Jersey City, New Jersey, 1866 (Box 32, Folder 673)
  - Jesup, Morris Ketchum, undated (Box 32, Folder 674)
  - Johnson, Andrew: Senate Impeachment Ticket, 1868 (Box 32, Folder 675)
  - Johnson, Bascom, 1966-1967 (Box 32, Folder 676)
  - Johnson, Electa Amanda (Wright), 1925 (Box 32, Folder 677)
  - Johnson, Henry, 1823 (Box 32, Folder 678)
  - Johnson, James Hutchins, 1857 (Box 32, Folder 679)
  - Johnson, Lucy F. (Hall), 1889 (Box 32, Folder 680)
  - Johnson, Noadiah, 1833 (Box 32, Folder 681)
  - Johnson, Samuel, 1843-1883, undated (Box 32, Folder 682)
  - Johnson, Samuel William, 1888-1892 (Box 32, Folder 683)
  - Johnson, Stephen (father and son), 1757-1791 (Box 32, Folder 684)
  - Johnston, John, 1867 (Box 32, Folder 685)
  - Jones, Samuel, 1821 (Box 32, Folder 686)
  - Jones, Seaborn, 1828 (Box 32, Folder 687)
  - Joyce, Charles Herbert, 1878 (Box 32, Folder 688)
  - Judd, Sylvester, 1842 (Box 32, Folder 689)
  - Judd, Truman O., 1856-1885 (Box 32, Folder 690)
  - Judson, Andrew Thompson, 1836-1844 (Box 32, Folder 691)
- K - L, Series V
  - Kagarov, Eugene Georgievich, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 692)
  - Kaliazin (Tver Province), Russia, Lemsio, 1891 (Box 33, Folder 693)
  - Kane, John Kintzing, 1838 (Box 33, Folder 694)
  - Kane, Thomas Leiper, 1850 (Box 33, Folder 695)
  - Keeney, Seth A. B., 1847-1885, undated (Box 33, Folder 696)
  - Keller, Helen Adams, 1942 (Box 33, Folder 697)
  - Kellogg, Bela, undated (Box 33, Folder 698)
  - Kellogg Family, 1721-1845, undated (Box 33, Folder 699)
  - Kemble, John Mitchell, 1848-1850 (Box 33, Folder 700)
  - Kemp, Harry, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 701)
  - Kendall, William Sergeant, 1896-1927, undated (Box 33, Folder 702)
  - Kennaday, Paul, 1908-1910 (Box 33, Folder 703)
  - Kennan, George Frost, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 704)
  - Kennedy, J. D., 1886 (Box 33, Folder 705)
  - Kennedy, Jacqueline (Bouvier), 1963 (Box 33, Folder 706)
  - Kennedy, John Fitzgerald, 1955-1962 (Box 34, Folder 707-709)
  - Kennedy, Robert Stewart, 1880 (Box 34, Folder 710)
  - Kent, Henry Watson, 1907 (Box 34, Folder 711)
  - Kershner, Jefferson Engel, 1894 (Box 34, Folder 712)
  - Kesser, Hermann, undated (Box 34, Folder 713)
  - Key, Marshall, 1837 (Box 34, Folder 714)
  - Kidd, William, undated (Box 34, Folder 715)
  - Kilbourn, John, 1829 (Box 34, Folder 716)
  - Kilbourne, Frederick Wilkinson, 1927-1941, undated (Box 34, Folder 717)
  - Kimball, Richard Burleigh, 1875 (Box 34, Folder 718)
  - Kimberly, Dennis, 1829-1857, undated (Box 34, Folder 719)
  - King, Horatio, 1890 (Box 34, Folder 720)
  - King, Rufus, 1825 (Box 34, Folder 721)
  - Kingman, Edward Dyer, 1940 (Box 34, Folder 722)
  - Kingsbury, Jacob, 1812-1814 (Box 34, Folder 723)
  - Kipling, Rudyard, 1896 (Box 34, Folder 724)
  - Kirby, Reynold Marvin, [1831?] (Box 34, Folder 725)
  - Kirkland, Caroline Matilda (Stansbury), undated (Box 34, Folder 726)
  - Kirtland, Jared Potter, 1874 (Box 34, Folder 727)
  - Knights Templars, Cambridge, Mass., 1920 (Box 34, Folder 728)
  - Knox, Henry, 1785 (Box 34, Folder 729)
  - Koehler, Sylvester Rosa and Walter J., 1888 (Box 35, Folder 730)
  - Kohut, George, 1916 (Box 35, Folder 731)
  - Kortholt, Sebastianus, undated (Box 35, Folder 732)
  - Kountze, Luther Collection, 1859-1921 (Box 35, Folder 733)
  - Kropotkin, Petr Aleksieevich, undated (Box 35, Folder 734)
  - Kruseman, J., 1829 (Box 35, Folder 735)
  - Kujawski, Piotr, undated (Box 35, Folder 736)
  - Lafayette, Marie Joseph Paul Yves Roch Gilbert du Matier, 1826-1828 (Box 35, Folder 737)
  - Lamb, Martha Joanna Reed (Nash), 1880 (Box 35, Folder 738)
  - Langley, A. R., 1787 (Box 35, Folder 739)
  - Lanman, Abigail (Trumbull), 1824 (Box 35, Folder 740)
  - Lanman, Charles, undated (Box 35, Folder 741)
  - Lanman, Peter Jr., 1852 (Box 35, Folder 742)
  - Larned, Joseph Nelson, 1895 (Box 35, Folder 743)
  - Laurence, John, 1807 (Box 35, Folder 744)
  - Laut, Agnes Christina, 1924-1926 (Box 35, Folder 745)
  - Law Notebook, undated (Box 35, Folder 746)
  - Lawrence, David, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 747)
  - Lawrence, Thomas Edward, 1923-1924 (Box 35, Folder 748)
  - Lear, Tobias, 1788, 1905 (Box 35, Folder 749)
  - Ledyard, Eben, 1785 (Box 35, Folder 750)
  - Lee, George Washington Custis, 1873, undated (Box 35, Folder 751)
  - Lee, H. B., 1816 (Box 35, Folder 752)
  - Lee, Henry, 1794 (Box 35, Folder 753)
  - Lee, Robert Edward, 1842 (Box 35, Folder 754)
  - Lee, William Henry Fitzhugh, 1886 (Box 35, Folder 755)
  - Leete, Pelatiah family, 1738-1826 (Box 35, Folder 756)
  - Leggal, Jane E., 1878 (Box 35, Folder 757)
  - Leisenring, Edward Barnes Collection, 1795-1928 (Box 35, Folder 758)
  - Lent, William Bement, 1892-1893 (Box 35, Folder 759)
  - Lesch, Ferdinande, 1940-1947 (Box 35, Folder 760)
  - Lester, Timothy, 1846-1849 (Box 35, Folder 761)
  - Lewis, James Davis, 1847-1848 (Box 35, Folder 762)
  - Lincoln, Abraham, 1842-1864 (Box 35, Folder 763)
  - Lind-Goldschmidt, Jenny Maria, [1851?] (Box 35, Folder 764)
  - Lindsley, Charles Augustus, 1889 (Box 35, Folder 765)
  - Lines, Henry, 1865-1883, undated (Box 35, Folder 766)
  - Linnell, Mary Belle, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 767)
  - Livermore, Mary Ashton Rice, 1894-1905, undated (Box 36, Folder 768)
  - Livingston, Ann, 1817 (Box 36, Folder 769)
  - Livingston, Edward, 1832 (Box 36, Folder 770)
  - Livingston, Henry Brockholst, 1795 (Box 36, Folder 771)
  - Livingstone, David, 1845 (Box 36, Folder 772)
  - Lloyd, Wildon, 1906, 1912 (Box 36, Folder 773)
  - Lockwood, Rev. James, 1761-1767 (Box 36, Folder 774)
  - Lodge, Henry Cabot, 1919 (Box 36, Folder 775)
  - Lodge, John Davis, 1952 (Box 36, Folder 776)
  - Loeb, William, 1901 (Box 36, Folder 777)
  - Longfellow, Alice M., 1909 (Box 36, Folder 778)
  - Loomis, Arphaxed, 1827 (Box 36, Folder 779)
  - Loomis, Hezekiah, 1804-1805 (Box 36, Folder 780)
  - Lopez Barrena, Josef Nicholas, [1796?] (Box 36, Folder 781)
  - Lossing, Benson John, 1872, undated (Box 36, Folder 782)
  - Louthan, George W., 1863-1865 (Box 36, Folder 783)
  - Lovell, John Epy, 1822-1896 (Box 37, Folder 784)
  - [Low, William Whittemore?], 1852-1869 (Box 37, Folder 785)
  - Lowe, Charles, 1867 (Box 37, Folder 786)
  - Lowell, Delmar Rial, undated (Box 37, Folder 787)
  - Lowell, James Russell, 1889, undated (Box 37, Folder 788)
  - Lukens, Caspar P., 1847 (Box 37, Folder 789)
  - Lumpkin, John Henry, 1857 (Box 37, Folder 790)
  - Lunn, Francis, 1828 (Box 37, Folder 791)
  - Luther, Flavel Sweeten, 1909 (Box 37, Folder 792)
  - Lyman, David, 1854 (Box 37, Folder 793)
  - Lyman, Joseph, 1795-1801 (Box 37, Folder 794)
  - Lyman, Theodore, 1884 (Box 37, Folder 795)
  - Lyon, Asa, 1816 (Box 37, Folder 796)
  - Lyon, Elizabeth, 1817 (Box 37, Folder 797)
  - Lyon, Ephraim Family, 1840-1893, undated (Box 37, Folder 798)
- M, Series VI
  - McCartree, Peter M., 1814 (Box 38, Folder 799)
  - McClellan, Ellen Mary (Marcy), 1888 (Box 38, Folder 800)
  - McCosh, James, undated (Box 38, Folder 801)
  - MacCracken, Henry Noble, 1914 (Box 38, Folder 802)
  - McCurdy, Charles Johnson, 1845-1889 (Box 38, Folder 803)
  - McDonald, Alexander, 1814 (Box 38, Folder 804)
  - McDonald, Andrew Y., 1862 (Box 38, Folder 805)
  - MacDonald, George, 1872 (Box 38, Folder 806)
  - MacDonald, Jeanne, undated (Box 38, Folder 807)
  - MacDonald, Mary (Bartlett), undated (Box 38, Folder 808)
  - McGregor, Donald Rait, 1959-1977, undated (Box 38, Folder 809)
  - McHenry, James, 1800 (Box 38, Folder 810)
  - Mack Family, 1852-1883 (Box 38, Folder 811)
  - McKee, Andrew, 1765 (Box 38, Folder 812)
  - McLane, Louis, 1832 (Box 38, Folder 813)
  - McMillen, Drury Albert, 1944-1946 (Box 38, Folder 814)
    Scope and Contents
    Consists of a manuscript copy of "Celestial navigation research" by D. A. McMillen, correspondence to and from W.V.B Findley concerning the presentation of the copy to Yale President Charles Seymour; and a photograph captioned "Sao Paulo State Airways" depicting McMillen and others.
  - McNab, John Forsyth, 1838 (Box 38, Folder 815)
  - McNeal, Robert, undated (Box 38, Folder 816)
  - McNiel, John, 1829 (Box 38, Folder 817)
  - McRae, Mrs., 1863 (Box 38, Folder 818)
  - Madison, James, 1789, 1837 (Box 38, Folder 819)
  - Mahon, Archibald, undated (Box 38, Folder 820)
  - Maistre, Joseph De, 1820 (Box 38, Folder 821)
  - Maltby Family, 1781-1853, undated (Box 38, Folder 822)
  - Mann, Benning, 1847 (Box 38, Folder 823)
  - Manning, Eliezer, 1793-1802, undated (Box 38, Folder 824)
  - Mansfield, Harvey Claflin Volumes I-II, 1932 (Box 39, Folder 825-826)
  - Manville, Burritt, 1881 (Box 39, Folder 827)
  - Marcy, William L., 1852 (Box 39, Folder 828)
  - Marks, Etta E., 1863 (Box 39, Folder 829)
  - Marriage Certificate, 1880 (Box 39, Folder 830)
  - Martin, Henry Marie Radegonde, 1906 (Box 39, Folder 831)
  - Martin, Luther, 1807 (Box 39, Folder 832)
  - Martin y Castro, Don Luis, 1897 (Box 39, Folder 833)
  - Mason, William, [1836?] (Box 39, Folder 834)
  - Massachusetts (Colony). Lieutenant Governor, 1770 (Box 39, Folder 835)
  - Massachusetts, Secretary, 1904 (Box 39, Folder 836)
  - Massachusetts-Legal Papers, 1690-1819, undated (Box 39, Folder 837)
  - Massachusetts Historical Society, 1857, 1883 (Box 39, Folder 838)
  - Masson, Louis Francois Rodrigue, 1895 (Box 39, Folder 839)
  - Mather, Cotton, 1682 (Box 39, Folder 840)
  - Matthews, William, 1880 (Box 39, Folder 841)
  - Maunder, Elwood R., 1958-1959 (Box 39, Folder 842-843)
  - Maury, W. A., 1868 (Box 39, Folder 844)
  - Mazzini, Giuseppe, undated (Box 39, Folder 845)
  - Mead, Melville Emery, 1885-1922, undated (Box 39, Folder 846)
  - Meade, George Gordon, 1864-1865 (Box 39, Folder 847)
  - Meagher, Thomas Francis, 1853 (Box 39, Folder 848)
  - Medill, Joseph, 1849 (Box 39, Folder 849)
  - [Mehlöef?], Anna, 1872 (Box 39, Folder 850)
  - Meigs, Josiah, 1816, 1821 (Box 39, Folder 851)
  - Meigs, Return Jonathan, 1808, 1816 (Box 39, Folder 852)
  - Meister, Georg, 1692 (Box 39, Folder 853)
  - Mejdell, Glor Thorvald, 1890 (Box 39, Folder 854)
  - Melchior, Kurt Werner, 1949 (Box 40, Folder 855)
  - Melcombe, George Bubb Dodington, baron, undated (Box 40, Folder 856)
  - Mendenhall, Harlan George, 1912-1934 (Box 40, Folder 857)
  - Mercer, Robert W., 1877 (Box 40, Folder 858)
  - Meserve, Frederick Hill, 1953 (Box 40, Folder 859)
  - Mesius, Caspar, 1612 (Box 40, Folder 860)
  - Metropolitan Club, 1873 (Box 40, Folder 861)
  - Mexico, 1693, 1814-67, undated (Box 40, Folder 862-868)